Guide to the Living Stage records 1965-2001
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 1: Administrative and financial files, 1965-2000
  - Financials and correspondence, 1965-1996
    - Love Letters on Living Stage Productions, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Love Letters from Season Performance Groups, 1967-1984 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Love Letters from Non-Residencies, 1968-1992 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Love Letters from Non-Residencies, 1969-1996 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Love Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Love Letters, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Love Letters from Prisons, 1974-1991 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Love Letters from Residencies, 1990-1992 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Love Letters from Residencies, 1990-1992 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Love Letters Wrap, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Love Letters Benefit, March 1993 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Lovers of L.S Benefit, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Lovers of Living Stage Correspondence, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Memos from Ruth, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Mental Health Benefit, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Merchandising Info and Expenses, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Michigan Festival, May 20, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Mike Raymond Letter, Julie Trahan, June 17, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Misc Bills, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Misc Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Montgomery Schools, July 22, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Morristown College and Federal City College, 1972-1974 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - National Council on Arts, Frederick County, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - NCTE, April 7, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - NEA Conference of the Arts, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - New Orleans Public Schools, June 18, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - New Orleans Public Schools, June 19, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - New Space Acquisition Financials, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Newsletter, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Newsletter Originals, circa 1980s (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Nina Reigger Response to Fundraising Mailer, November 1984 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Notes, Memos, Oral Correspondence, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Notes, Memos, and Correspondence, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Operating Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Parents and Child Care Resources, December 20, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Pat Harbour Letters, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Peter Gabb and Lillian Lenz, June 18, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Phonathon Ally and Info, 1981-1983 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools, December 15, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Prints, Records [LP's] for Tri-School, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Programming Correspondence, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Receipts, Invoices, and Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Rhode Island College, July 2, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Richard Simon, September 20, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Mrs. Robert Longsworth, June 11, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Sacred Heart of Jesus High, June 15, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Samuels Correspondence, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - School System Information and Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - School Program Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Smithsonian Associates, Wayne Fenton, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Smithsonian Institute, April 24, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Special Projects Budgets, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - St. Cecelia's Academy and Robert Pugh Letter, September 16, 1970 and June 13, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - St. Luke's Benefit, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Sugar Ray Leonard Correspondence, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Susan's Benefit Report, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Ted Jacob Letters, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Thank You Letter Examples, 1985-1987 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - UCLA, April 14, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - University of Hawaii, February 9, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Museum Love Letters, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Waukegan Township High Ontario Dept. of Education, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - West Virginia Arts and Humanities Council, May 7, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - West Virginia Arts and Humanities Council - Nancy Hawks, May 7, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - West Virginia Arts and Humanities Council - Zelda Fichandler, May 7, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Wind in the Windows Love Letters, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Wind in the Windows Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Wind in the Windows Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - White Oak Jr High, E. Brooke Lee School, July 15-18, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Wofford College, DC Teache's College, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Workshop [Love] Letters, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Worthy Association of Youth RAP, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Xerox Budget Information, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Yorkshire Theatre Co, October 19, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Youth Crime Control Project Lorton Youth Center, 1971 and 1974 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Public relations and printed pieces, 1966-1995
    - 17th Season Solicitation Letter, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - 25th Anniversary Info Packets and Envelopes, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Acquisition Copy/Artwork, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - All Power to the Imagination Brochure and Imagination Calendar, Undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Articles, 1967-1981 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Articles, 1982-1988 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Articles, 1982-1988 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Articles on Living Stage, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Auction Brochure, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - B.J's PR Project, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Basta Handout, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Basta Nuclear War Program, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Basta Press, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Basta Tickets, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Benefit Concert and Performance Posters, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Bob Alexander Newsletter Interview, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Booking Now, Undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Boston Reviews, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Boston Reviews, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Brochure Development, 1982-1986 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Brochures, mailings, late 1970s (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Building Press, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Building Press Conference, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Cas' Japan Article on L.S, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Catherine's Speech to Join Together Fellows, August 1992 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Catherine's Testimony - DC Commission of the Arts and Humanities, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Catherine's Testimony to DC Commission on the Arts and Humanities, February 11, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - CD News Winter Issue, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Children Theatre Press Releases, 1967-1970 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Community Outreach Letters, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Curriculum Enrichment Press Releases, 1967-1970 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Danny Ditther Author Visits Area, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Donation Solicitation Letters, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Forms, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Fundraiser Envelopes and Pamphlets, Undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Fundraiser Letters, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Fundraiser Letters, circa 1980s (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Georgetown University, November 12, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Hasbro Article, Fall 1985 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Healing Our Society through Creativity, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Hewe's Article - Congressional Record, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - I Know Another Way, Undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - I Know Another Way... Pamphlets, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Information Dissemination Organs (Newsletters), 1978 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - In-House Articles, 1983-1984 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Invitations for Openings, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Let There Be a New World, Undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Letter and Reply Envelopes, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Lettershop and Solicitations, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Life Magazine, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Living Stage Touches Home George Mason Junior-Senior High School, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Lynched Hopes and other Production Pamphlets, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Mailings, Press Releases, 1969-1975 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Media Material, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Misc. Printed Pieces and PR, 1979-1983 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - National Committee Arts for the Handicapped - Programs and Posters, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - New Orleans Workshop Press Releases, 1967-1970 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - New Spirit LS Pose, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - News in Brief, June 1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - News Releases, 1991-1995 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Newsletter, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Newsletter, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Newsletter, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Newsletter, 1981-1983 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Newsletter - Bob Alexander Day, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter - Fall, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Newsletter - Spring, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Newsletter - Spring, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Newsletter - Winter, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Newsletters and Pamphlets, 1969-1973 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Articles, late 1960s early 1970s (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Old Lovers of Living Stage Form, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Old Releases, 1974-1979 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Old Thank You Letters, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Outreach Project, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Overseas Press Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - P.R - P.R - P.R, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Pledge Cards, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - PR Misc, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Press (Recent), 1990 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Press Clips, 1982-1983 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Press Kit, Company Resumes, Bob's Resume, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases, 1967-1970 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases, 1967-1970 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases, 1985-1987 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Press Releases, 1985-1989 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Press Releases, brochures, etc, 1984-1985 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Printed Pieces - Announcements and Benefit Ads, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Printed Pieces Bundles, circa 1970s (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Printed Pieces, Press, etc, circa late 1980s (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Printed Pieces, Press, etc - Actors Info, circa 1980s (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Printed PR, Flyers, Workshops, etc, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Printed Press and Pamphlets, circa 1990s (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Public Performance Invites, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Public Performances Pamphlets and Programs, 1991-1993 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Publicity, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Remarks by Remi Bosseau and Olympia Dukakis re: Living Stage, April 17, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Renwick Art Museum Pamphlet, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Rob Alexander Day Press Release, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Robert Alexander's Speaking Engagements, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Speeches to NoVA Teachers, 1966-1967 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Stationary, circa 1980s (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Stationary 20th, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Summer Youth Employment - Committee on Labor Testimony, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Temple Award Acceptance - Noetic Sciences, June 1992 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Testimonies to Committee on Human Service, February 19, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Testimony on ADASA, July 15, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - The Root of Rage and Images, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - This Company is for Children - Article by Ned Chaillet, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Treasure Island Articles, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Tri-School Photos and Releases, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Tri-School Programs Press Releases, 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - TV and Radio Spots for Kiddie Plays, 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Vanessa's Testimony at DC Public Health Commission, June 15, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Washington Post Advertising, 1976-1979 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Working Letters, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Workshop Brochures, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Workshop Press Releases, 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Young Audience - Newsclippings, December 1982 (Box 56, Folder 29)
- Series 2: Artistic and workshop files, 1966-2001
  Series 2. Artistic and Workshop Files (1966-2001), which is split into 3 subseries, contains the creative aspects of the Living Stage, including details about residencies and the personnel of the Company, as well as workshop reports, scripts, and "Jams". Subseries 2.1 Residency and Personnel Files contains all documents related to the people of the Living Stage, including casting information and details about out of state residencies (including those in Stockholm, Boston, Pittsburgh, New York and others). Subseries 2.2 Production Reports and Workshops encompasses the output of the Living Stage Theatre Company in the form of workshops, which are series of performances put on at schools, museums, and communities, and the production reports which sought to analyze audience reception of and reaction to these performances. Look to the "Baltimore Incident" for an excellent example of how contentious and revolutionary the Living Stage's performances were. Subseries 2.3 Production Files and Scripts, while small, contains items related to the Living Stage's "Jams" including scripts, research, and other assorted play files.
  - Residency and personnel files, 1966-1994
    - Administrative Assistant (Resumes), 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Arizona Tour, May 1979 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Atlanta and Detroit Residency and Support Letters, 1987-1988 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Atlanta Residency, April 1988 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Baltimore Archives Images, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Baltimore Residency, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Boston, April 28-May 9, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Boston, April 1986 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Boston Residency, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Casting, Spring 1994 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Casting, circa 1970s (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Charleston S.C Residency, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Chicago Residency, May 1989 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Cleveland, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Cleveland Residency, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Company Bios, Undated (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - DC Residency, 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - DC Residency, 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Detroit, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Detroit Residency, April 1988 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - East Berlin, November 1981 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Hammond Indiana Residency Info, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Hartford Connecticut Residency Info, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Hasbro/Pittsburgh Residencies, Undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - List of Past Residencies, 1966-1980 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Milwaukee Performing Arts Center, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Minneapolis Residency, May 1988 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - New York City Residency, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Old Casting Notices, circa 1980s (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Operation Crossroads Africa Personnel Files, 1982-1985 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Philadelphia PA Residency, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh, March 3-7, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh - "Images", March 3, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh - Second Release, February 1986 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Residency, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Residencies, 1960s-1980s (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Residencies Format Outline, Undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Residency Transcript - Chicago, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Residency Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Residency Budget Information, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Residency Info, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Residency Packet, circa 1980s (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Robert Thurber Resume, circa 1980s (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Skola Residency Planning, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Stockholm, May 1990 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Sweden Residency - Press Release, April 1990 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Tiber Island Residency, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - West Coast Residency, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - University of Michigan Residency Info, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Production reports and workshops, 1967-2001
    - Ads for Workshops, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Ads for Workshops, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Afro-centric Workshop, 1990-1991 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Amazing Life Games 2-4's, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Amazing Life Games 5-7's, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - American Shakespeare Workshops, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Arena School Program, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Audience Suggestions Evaluations, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Ballou, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Ballou Evaluation, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Ballou Evaluations, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Ballou High School Evaluation, 1983-1984 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Ballou High School Evaluations, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Ballou Workshop, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Baltimore Incident, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Baltimore Incident, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Bookings, 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Boston, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Bowie College, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Burning Tree Elementary, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - CAREL (Central Atlantic Regional Educational Laboratory), 1968 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - CAREL Workshop, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - CAREL-Arena Theatre Program for Young Children, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Children First, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Children First Workshop Schedules and Reports, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Children's Theatre, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Children's Theatre Workshop, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Class Reports, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - College Tours, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Community Service Project Evaluation, 1983-1984 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Company Evaluation Notes - Sharpe Health, 1978-1979 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Company Evaluations - Fairhill, Franklin, Sherman, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - CSP Monthly Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - CYS (COBA) Evaluations (copies), 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - D.C Jail Evaluation for Women, 1983-1984 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - D.C Jail Evaluations, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - D.C Jail Workshop, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - D.C Receiving Home Workshop (63-64 Fairhill), 1980 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - D.C Schools Workshops, Undated (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - December Public Performance, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - DOE Workshop Appendix, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Evaluation with Marty Boyer, 1998-1999 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Evaluations, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Evaluations - Handwritten Copies, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Evaluations (Franklin and Fairhill), 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Fairhill Workshops, 1979-1980 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Fall Workshops, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Fall Workshops, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Fall Workshops, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Fall Workshops, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Films Workshop, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Foundry in Old Vat Workshop, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin Sherman Production Notes, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Garrison Elementary (copies), 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Garrison Elementary Season Evaluation, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Hawaii Workshops, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Hawaii Workshops, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - High School Series Production Reports, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Holland and TIP Workshop and Evaluations, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Holland Workshop, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Holly Park-Glen Echo Evaluation, January-March 1976 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - I had a Dream: Group Notes and Evaluations, 1988-1989 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - I HAD Evaluation, Questionnaires and Typed Poetry Orig, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - I Had: Production Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - I.H.A.D. Evaluation, 1991-1993 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - IHAD Special Reports - Evaluations, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Improvisational Process and The Myth of the Black Underclass, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Inspire Festival, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Jackson School, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Jenn Evaluation, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Kidz Biz, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Kimball Elementary, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Kimball Season Evaluation, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - KOBA, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - KOBA Season Evaluation, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Lead Sheets for Workshops, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Learning Stage Evaluations, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Letters from Summer Workshops, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - London/Paris Tour, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Lorton, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Lorton Workshop, 1978-1980 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Lorton/CTF Season Evaluation, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Love Theatre Workshop Report, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Maui Community College Workshop, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Mental Health Evaluations, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Metrobus Workshop, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Michigan Festival, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Morgan School, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - National Collection of the Fine Arts, 1968-1970 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - NCFA Incident, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - NCTE Convention Workshop, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - NCTE Convention Workshop, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - New Orleans Workshop, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - New Theatre Festival, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - One Shots Workshops, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Other Children's Theatres, 1968-1970 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Other Children's Theatres, 1968-1971 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Peace (Facing History and Ourselves) Nuclear Program, 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Performance Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Performance Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Performance Reports II, 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Performance Reports II, 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Performance Reports Vol. 1, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Performance Reports Vol. 1, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Performances, 1969-1980 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Performances, 1969-1982 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Press for Workshops, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Press for Workshops, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Production Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Production Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Production Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Production Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Production Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Production Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Production Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Production Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Production Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Production Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Production Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Production Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Production Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Production Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Production Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 4)